In conclusion, I would like to see
Tachikawa's opening ceremony this time.
When I first thought about what I
wanted to do,
the first thing that came to my mind
was to do a live show.
I wanted to do something related to the
Koto Kisei.
But I couldn't do it.
I was so frustrated.
I felt like I couldn't do anything.
Ready?
Yes!
Good morning!
I'm wearing makeup.
I haven't done anything yet.
It's okay to do a little bit.
I'm not going to do this much.
Today is the day.
The first day.
I've seen the stage.
It's not hot but I feel like I'm in the
arena.
Yes, it's like an arena.
Who is this lip roll?
It's easy to tell.
I can tell as soon as I enter.
I can tell right away.
I'm going to put on a makeup.
I was thinking about whether to do
half-twin or half-twin dance.
I'm going to look back or look up.
I don't know which one I'm going to
look.
I haven't seen it yet.
Have you seen the stage?
No.
You should see it.
It's amazing.
I saw it yesterday.
It was more amazing.
It was more powerful.
I was so scared of the truck.
It was quite high.
It was really...
My legs were around here.
I saw it.
I saw it a while ago.
Please look forward to the next.
My legs are like this.
I'm going to take a picture here.
From here, it's my height.
I'll introduce today's guest menu.
It's on top.
It's a combination of Katsudon and
Muffin.
I'm alone.
You are cute.
20 minutes left for the deadline!
You're so handsome~~
you're handsome~~~
You're gonna make me cry
Do you like my hair?
Do you like it?
Let's go with two!
Isn't it cute?
It's so cute!
The second one is
wearing a shirt inside
with a shirt with a hood.
It's a ribbon.
Please look forward to it.
Please check which one is which at the
live.
We'll do our best.
Bye-bye.
This program is brought to you by six
people who are active to promote
something.
We challenge various things and raise
the excitement barometer of the world!
Please register your channel.
I put my tear bags in my bag.
Did I put too many?
No, you did.
I put a lot today.
I did.
Today's makeup is summer girl.
Spring, spring, spring, spring live.
Like the last live, spring, spring,
spring, spring live.
Today is summer live.
I put on makeup.
I have a cat today.
I don't usually have a cat.
But it looks like summer.
Do I look good?
Am I cute?
I'll do my best.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching!
I'll do my best!
I'm wearing a miyagi-gai today.
I'll change my hair style.
I'll wear this dandelion-shaped one.
I'll change my clothes.
I'll do my best!
I'm going to put on my shoes.
I can't go in.
Yes! You've got to take a selfie this
morning!
Here I go!
Mine too, mine too.
I like Kaburin.
I have a Kaburin book.
Please read it.
We eat Kaburin in this way, don't we?
I'm not sure what we eat.
We eat the same way.
We eat Katsu.
Katsu?
We eat it all the time.
What is it?
It's so good.
Thank you very much.
I forgot how many I was trying to say.
I have something to say to OJYORI
later.
Is OJYORI here?
It doesn't open.
It's open.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
OJYORI, I have something to say to you.
What is the new song, Love Park?
It's Julia.
There's a scene where I'm petting Nana.
And I'm like,
I'm so cute!
I'm jealous.
She is really cute.
When I was dancing, I couldn't
concentrate on the choreography.
The girl in front of me was so cute.
I was dancing in front of her, but I
couldn't concentrate on the
choreography.
She is so cute that I can't help but
smile while dancing.
I can't see the live choreography
because it's a tropical song.
She is really cute.
What are you going to do?
I was just called by that.
I was so embarrassed.
So, I didn't tell the teacher who made
me a frill, but I was looking at her and
I thought,
I'm sorry.
Please stand up.
Thank you for my ass.
Thank you for watching.
Please pay attention to the dance.
Please.
I'll go back.
Cute.
The cutest.
It's the first time I've seen two
hairpins.
Right?
It's pretty cute.
I'll start.
I'm done.
I'll do my best to not make you
nervous.
I'll do my best.
The first day of the event.
Good morning.
Please.
It's cute.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for watching.
ていれ・みゅいあのん
enkajima
I don't know this re Treasury
At the end of Sonic Adventure, at the
very end,
there is a big sound that goes, bang!
We will actually do that now.
So, please be prepared.
Are you facing this way?
The other side.
The sound starts from there.
We will play the actual sound.
Yes.
Please take a picture.
The sound is going to be loud.
3, 2, 1
Thank you for watching!
I wonder where everyone went That'd be
so funny
Oh my god!
No way!
Well,
how about you guys?
How do you feel about the next song?
I'm a little nervous.
I'm nervous!
I see.
I couldn't speak.
I was so surprised.
Anyway...
Bye!
I thought I could do it because I was
wearing earphones, but I couldn't see
all three of them.
But the PR staff in front of me was
surprised, too.
This is the end!
Staff has come to help with the
filming.
Who's voice makes the AGAIN?
We're taking a break here.
Best cat
Nice catch
That is Ume
All right
Thank you for your viewing.
「Sakai Sakai ni... 」
1, 2, 3, 4!
graduate school
We ran through the opening ceremony
We called the audience along the way
Accept this torch
It's a miracle, it's your fault.
Let's have more fun tomorrow.
I'll always draw you.
You are important.
I'm going to the next location.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'm just pretending to be a person
who's passing by, but I'm really looking
at the camera.
The audition is over.
Oh, I'm winning. Everyone is eating.
I'm winning.
I'm the best.
There are a lot of delicious food.
Let's go.
I'm not done yet.
3, 2, 1.
I'm going to eat.
Wow.
Awesome.
I'm going to eat.
Look at Aki-chan!
Aahh nice spot come back
Wow!
I'm so happy!
Wait!
I've never seen such a picture!
I've only seen 4 pictures!
Oh my god!
6 people!
Yay!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Can we have one later?
I have 20 minutes left until the show.
There is a curtain here.
I mean, there is a curtain.
There is a curtain with a curtain.
If I turn it over, you can see me.
I'm going to be seen.
I want to be seen.
But it would be the worst if I was
seen.
Where is it?
Out of here.
lol
I'm not exposed.
I'm not sure if I can speak.
I enjoyed the thrill.
I can't do it anymore.
I'll do my best.
Bye.
I changed my clothes.
This is the first costume.
When I wear this, I can only see the
light blue costume.
It's light blue, but when I take it
off, it becomes purple.
I have to move a lot today.
I'm not that far away.
I'm close to the costume.
When I take it off, it becomes purple.
Isn't it great that it becomes this?
It changes the pattern.
I changed my clothes.
It's cute.
I'm hiding here.
Yes.
I'm like this.
Look at my hair.
It's a sudden bangs.
I got my hair tied up so that I can't
move.
I'll go upstairs.
I'm back!
I think the before and after of my
appearance in the morning is amazing.
I'll do my best in the real performance
soon!
I'll find you all!
I like it!
It's so hot.
It's cute.
I used to have this hairstyle when I
was a little girl.
I remember you had two of them.
I can't do it.
You don't like twin tails, do you?
I can't do it when I get older.
It's your time.
I'll do my best to talk about real
things.
I'll do my best.
Bye!
I wonder why, when I smile, the world
seems to shine
I can turn my umbrella and feel
relaxed, because I can't walk without it
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere,
and I'm still getting wet somewhere
I wonder if it's cold
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere,
and I'm still getting wet somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
There's still a view I've never seen
before
Come on, let's go anywhere
I thought that the live show at the
Arena was the best!
And everyone is so cute!
Their clothes are cute, their costumes
are cute, it's the best!
That's what I thought
Please subscribe to our channel and
click the like button!
We're waiting for your comments and
feedback!
Everyone's purple!
I'm Anjouria!
Bye bye!
I can still say it now, right?
I remember the reason I saw you, and
the time I got lost
Even if it rains, I'll go wherever I
can to make you smile
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of rain drops is ringing
I'll play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of rain drops is ringing
I'll wear a rainbow dress